http://www.squirelocks.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BACKGROUND:Henry Squire & Sons Limited understands that your privacy is  important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used.  We respect and value the privacy of everyone whose personal data we use  and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described  here, and in a manner that is consistent with Our obligations and your  rights under the law.We collect your data in the following ways:
When you use our website (‘Our Site’) – www.squirelocks.co.ukWhen we sell and deliver goods and services to youWhen we purchase goods and services from youWhen we want to deliver a direct marketing campaign
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you  understand it. If you are using our site your acceptance of Our Privacy  Policy is deemed to occur upon your first use of Our Site. If you do not  accept and agree with this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our Site  immediately.1.   Definitions and InterpretationIn this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:
“personal data”    means any and  all data that relates to an identifiable person who can be directly or  indirectly identified from that data. In this case, it means personal  data that you give to Us via Our Site. This definition shall, where  applicable, incorporate the definitions provided in the EU Regulation  2016/679 – the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”); and “We/Us/Our”means Henry  Squire & Sons Limited, a limited company registered in England under  company number 88907, whose registered address is Arbor House, Broadway  North, Walsall WS1 2AN, and whose main trading address is Hilton Cross  Business Park, Cannock Road, Featherstone, WV10 7QZ.
2.   Information About Us2.1   Our Site is owned and operated by Henry Squire & Sons  Limited, a limited company registered in England under company number88907, whose registered address is Arbor House, Broadway North,  Walsall, WS1 2AN and whose main trading address is Hilton Cross Business  Park, Cannock Road, Featherstone, WV10 7QZ.2.2   Our VAT number is 100 1214 65.2.3   Stephen Watson is in charge of data protection for Us and can be contacted at dataprotection@henry-squire.co.uk or by post at Henry Squire & Sons Limited, Hilton Cross Business Park, Cannock Road, Featherstone, WV10 7QZ3.   What Does This Policy Cover?This Privacy Policy applies to your use of Our Site and Our Site  may contain links to other websites. Please note that We have no control  over how your data is collected, stored or used by other websites and  We advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before  providing any data to them.4.   Your Rights4.1   As a data subject, you have the following rights under the  GDPR, which this Policy and Our use of personal data have been designed  to uphold:4.1.1   The right to be informed about Our collection and use of personal data;4.1.2   The right of access to the personal data we hold about you (see section 12);4.1.3   The right to rectification if any personal data We hold  about you is inaccurate or incomplete (please contact Us using the  details in section 13);4.1.4   The right to be forgotten – i.e. the right to ask Us to  delete any personal data we hold about you (We only hold your personal  data for a limited time, as explained in section 6 but if you would like  Us to delete it sooner, please contact Us using the details in section  13);4.1.5   The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data;4.1.6   The right to data portability (obtaining a copy of your personal data to re-use with another service or organisation);4.1.7   The right to object to Us using your personal data for particular purposes;4.1.8   Rights with respect to automated decision making and profiling.4.2   If you have any cause for complaint about Our use of your  personal data, please contact Us using the details provided in section  13 and We will do Our best to solve the problem for you. If We are  unable to help, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the  UK’s supervisory authority, the Information Commissioner’s Office.4.3   For further information about your rights, please contact the  Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.5.   What Data Do We Collect?Depending upon your use of Our Site, We may collect some or all of the following personal and non-personal data:5.1    name;5.2    business/company name;5.3    job title;5.4    contact information such as home address, delivery address,  email addresses, telephone number depending on you are a business or an  individual;5.5    Payment details;5.6    Any other details required to fulfil our contract with you.6.   How Do We Use Your Data?6.1   All personal data is processed and stored securely, for no  longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was  first collected. We will comply with Our obligations and safeguard your  rights under the GDPR at all times. For more details on security see  section 7, below.6.2   Our use of your personal data will always have a lawful  basis, either because it is necessary for Our performance of a contract  with you, because you have consented to Our use of your personal data  (e.g. by subscribing to emails), or because it is in our legitimate  interests. Specifically, We may use your data for the following  purposes:6.2.1   Supplying Our products or services to you (please note that  We may require your personal data in order to enter into a contract  with you depending on the status of your business);6.2.2   Replying to emails from you;6.2.3   Market research;6.3   With your permission and/or where permitted by law, We may  also use your data for marketing purposes which may include contacting  you by email and telephone and post with information, news and offers on  Our products or services. We will not, however, send you any  unsolicited marketing or spam and will take all reasonable steps to  ensure that We fully protect your rights and comply with Our obligations  under the GDPR and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC  Directive) Regulations 2003.6.4   You have the right to withdraw your consent to Us using your personal data at any time, and to request that We delete it.6.5   We do not keep your personal data for any longer than is  necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected.  Data will therefore be retained for the following periods (or its  retention will be determined on the following bases):6.5.1   Except as required by applicable law or regulatory  requirements Henry Squire & Sons will retain your personal data for  as long as it believes is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the  personal data was collected (including for the meeting of any legal,  accounting or other reporting requirements);7.    How and Where Do We Store Your Data?7.1   We only keep your personal data for as long as We need to in  order to use it as described above in section 6, and/or for as long as  We have your permission to keep it.7.2   Some or all of your data may be stored within the UK and or  the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of all EU  member states, plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein). However some or  all of your data may be stored outside the EEA. You are deemed to accept  and agree to this by using Our Site and submitting information to Us.  If We do store data outside the EEA, We will take all reasonable steps  to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it would  be within the UK and under the GDPR.7.3   Data security is very important to Us, and to protect your  data We have taken suitable measures to safeguard and secure data  collected through Our Site by utilising data encryption, locked cabinets  and electronic password protection.8.   Do We Share Your Data?8.1   We may share your data with other companies in Our group for business purposes. This includes Our holding company.8.2   We may sometimes contract with third parties to supply  products and services to you on Our behalf. These may include payment  processing, delivery of goods, search engine facilities, advertising,  and marketing. In some cases, the third parties may require access to  some or all of your data. Where any of your data is required for such a  purpose, We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data will  be handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, Our  obligations, and the obligations of the third party under the law.8.3   We may compile statistics about the use of Our Site including  data on traffic, usage patterns, user numbers, sales, and other  information. All such data will be anonymised and will not include any  personally identifying data, or any anonymised data that can be combined  with other data and used to identify you. We may from time to time  share such data with third parties such as prospective investors,  affiliates, partners, and advertisers. Data will only be shared and used  within the bounds of the law.8.4   The third party data processors used by Us may be located  outside of the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of  all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein). Where We  transfer any personal data outside the EEA, We will take all reasonable  steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it  would be within the UK and under the GDPR.8.5   In certain circumstances, We may be legally required to share  certain data held by Us, which may include your personal data, for  example, where We are involved in legal proceedings, where We are  complying with legal requirements, a court order, or a governmental  authority. 9.   What Happens If Our Business Changes Hands?9.1   We may, from time to time, expand or reduce Our business and  this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part  of Our business. Any personal data that you have provided will, where it  is relevant to any part of Our business that is being transferred, be  transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling  party will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use  that data only for the same purposes for which it was originally  collected by Us.9.2   In the event that any of your data is to be transferred in  such a manner, you will not be contacted in advance and informed of the  changes.10.   How Can You Control Your Data?10.1   In addition to your rights under the GDPR, set out in  section 4, when you submit personal data via Our Site, you may be given  options to restrict Our use of your data. In particular, We aim to give  you strong controls on Our use of your data for direct marketing  purposes (including the ability to opt-out of receiving emails from Us  which you may do by unsubscribing using the links provided in Our emails  and at the point of providing your details).10.2   You may also wish to sign up to one or more of the  preference services operating in the UK: The Telephone Preference  Service (“the TPS”), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (“the  CTPS”), and the Mailing Preference Service (“the MPS”). These may help  to prevent you receiving unsolicited marketing. Please note, however,  that these services will not prevent you from receiving marketing  communications that you have consented to receiving.11.   Your Right to Withhold Information11.1   You may access certain areas of Our Site without providing  any data at all. However, to use all features and functions available on  Our Site you may be required to submit or allow for the collection of  certain data.12.   How Can You Access Your Data?You have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal data  held by Us (where such data is held). Under the GDPR, no fee is payable  and We will provide any and all information in response to your request  free of charge. Please contact Us for more details at Henry Squire &  Sons Limited, Hilton Cross Business Park, Cannock Road, Featherstone  WV10 7QZ.13.   Contacting UsIf you have any questions about Our Site or this Privacy Policy,  please contact Us by post at Henry Squire & Sons Limited, Hilton  Cross Business Park, Cannock Road, Featherstone WV10 7QZ. Please ensure  that your query is clear, particularly if it is a request for  information about the data We hold about you (as under section 12,  above).14.   Changes to Our Privacy PolicyWe may change this Privacy Policy from time to time (for example,  if the law changes). Any changes will be immediately posted on Our Site  and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy  on your first use of Our Site following the alterations. We recommend  that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
Keep me updated with
All News
Security Products
Bikelok
Motolok
Digital Security
All news
sign up
Follow us
Copyright © 2020 Squire. All rights reserved.
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
